<aiml version="1.0.1" encoding="UTF-8">
<!-- VeritasQuestions.aiml -->
		<category>
		<pattern>WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A GLOBAL AND LOCAL PRODUCT</pattern>
		<template>
			Global product groups local product names into a predefined name used by businesses on an international level. A local product represents the name being used by businesses within each country to determine the product of a policy, which can be the same as, a variation of or different to the global product name.
		</template>
		</category>
		<category>
		<pattern>WHAT IS YOUR NAME?</pattern>
		<template>
			My name is MuBot
		</template>
		</category>
        <category>
            <pattern>* ABOUT VERITAS</pattern>
            <template><srai>VERITAS</srai></template>
        </category>
        <category>
            <pattern>* AIM OF VERITAS</pattern>
            <template><srai>VERITAS</srai></template>
        </category>
        <category>
            <pattern>TELL ME ABOUT VERITAS</pattern>
            <template><srai>VERITAS</srai></template>
        </category>
        <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS VERITAS</pattern>
        <template>Veritas is ACIA's enterprise Data Warehouse platform which is hosted on an EC2 instance in the AWS Internal Production VPC.</template>
		</category>
        <category>
            <pattern>VERITAS</pattern>
            <template>
                The aim of Veritas is to provide both ACIA and Aon In-point colleagues with a platform to conduct advanced analytics along with providing broker and carrier insight.
            </template>
        </category>

    <!--category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS PREMIUM</pattern>
        <template>
            Is a datamart and it is available for consumption.
        </template>
    </category-->
	<category>
		<pattern>WHAT IS THE DIFFERENCE BETWEEN A GLOBAL AND LOCAL PRODUCT</pattern>
		<template>
			Global product groups local product names into a predefined name used by businesses on an international level. A local product represents the name being used by businesses within each country to determine the product of a policy, which can be the same as, a variation of or different to the global product name.
		</template>
	</category>

    <category>
        <pattern>* CARRIER</pattern>
        <template>
            An insurance or reinsurance company that insures or "carries" the insurance or reinsurance.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>* DEFINITION OF AN OPPORTUNITY</pattern>
        <template>
            Opportunities are defined as individual policies that are due to expire in the next 12 months. It can also be a grouping of policies that share expiration date
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS A DATA WAREHOUSE</pattern>
        <template>
            A data warehouse is a large store of data accumulated from a wide range of sources within a company and is used to guide management decisions.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS AN OLAP DATABASE</pattern>
        <template>
            OLAP is part of the broader category of business intelligence, which also encompasses relational database, report writing and data mining.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS A CUBE OF INFORMATION</pattern>
        <template>
            The Information Cube is a new 3D visualization technique for hierarchical information
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS A PIPELINE</pattern>
        <template>
             An activity, item of information, material, or product, that is between the starting point and the completion point is 'in pipeline
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS AIMS</pattern>
        <template>
             Aon Information Management System
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>* ACCESS TO VERITAS</pattern>
        <template>
            1. Request to be sent to Service Desk including business requirement for access and manager approval

			2. Service Desk to review request and confirm approval with Product Owner

			3. If requirements meet forward request to the DBA team

			4. DBA team to provide connection details (server/instance address, user credentials)
		</template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>* CONNECT TO VERITAS</pattern>
        <template>
             The DBA team will provide connection details (server/instance address, user credentials) that you can use to connect via any tool that can handle Veritas
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS A DATAMART</pattern>
        <template>
             The datamart is a subset of the data warehouse that is usually oriented to a specific business line or team. Datamarts are small slices of the data warehouse.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>* A CAPTIVE</pattern>
        <template>
             An insurance company that as its primary purpose, finances the risks of its owners or participants, i.e. the insurer is captive to the policyholder.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>HOW DOES A DATA WAREHOUSE WORK</pattern>
        <template>
             A data warehouse is constructed by integrating data from multiple heterogeneous sources
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT KIND OF THINGS CAN I DO IN VERITAS</pattern>
        <template>
             Veritas will consist of 4 different datamarts to enable analytics and reporting on 4 main functions.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>HOW OFTEN IS THE INFORMATION REFRESHED</pattern>
        <template>
             A further goal of the project is to ensure data can be refreshed in a more timely fashion. Initially this will be weekly. Ultimately this will be daily or even intra-day.
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT DOES VERITAS OFFER</pattern>
        <template>
             Veritas offers policy data available at lowest level of granularity
        </template>
    </category>

    <category>
        <pattern>WHAT IS TABLEAU</pattern>
        <template>
             Tableau is a software that produces a family of interactive data visualisation products focused on business intelligence
        </template>
    </category>


</aiml>